251 10th St. NW, C509 Atlanta, GA 30318 U.S.A.

# ChangSeok Oh

Profile: https://shivamidow.github.io E-mail: changseok@gnome.org Mobile: +1 (404) 740-7896

Open source enthusiast and hacker specializing in web technology and linux-based system. WebKit and GNOME project contributor. More than 8 years experience at major players in the industry. Looking for opportunities in Web browser, Web Security & Privacy, Kernel, and Computer Graphics.

Skills

WebKit, Blink/Chromium, GNOME, Linux, C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Objective-C, Java, OpenGL/OpenGL ES, Clutter, Computer Graphics, GTK+, eBPF, BCC, Ethereum, Git, OBS, Clang, LLVM, GStreamer, Tizen, Linux Perf, Bluetooth LE, React Native, Embedded system

Education

08/2017 - 08/2019 03/2000 - 06/2008 M.S. in Computer Science (Computer Systems, GPA: 3.87 / 4.0), Georgia Tech in Atlanta, GA, U.S.A. Dual B.E. in Digital Media and Computer Engineering, Ajou University in South Korea

## **Professional Experience**

06/2019 - present Intern at Igalia, S.L. in A Coruña, Spain • Bring ANGLE backend for WebGL to WebKitGTK 05/2019 - 08/2019 Intern at Samsung Research America in Mountain View, CA • Built an automated system that verifies UI of a watch app by using Tizen automation framework Profiled memory usage and revealed possible memory leak of a watch app by using Valgrind • Implemented file transfer via Bluetooth LE Software engineer at Collabora Ltd. in Cambridge, UK 08/2012 - 03/2016 • Developed hardware based compositing based on Clutter in WebKit • Resource efficient web browser based on GNOME Epiphany for Raspberry Pi 2+ Customized WebKit features and API set for Smart TV Alliance SDK 07/2008 - 08/2012 Assistant Software engineer at Samsung Electronics in Suwon, South Korea • Developed an in-house web layout engine for Smart TVs, Printers in C++ • Implemented WebGL and Accelerated Compositing in WebKit EFL by using OpenGL ES for Tizen Intern at Samsung Software Membership in Suwon, South Korea 07/2007 - 06/2008 • Developed a 3D racing game using DirectX on Windows (video)

### Academic Experience

08/2017 - 08/2019

## Research assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech

- Developed a defense system against micro DDoS by profiling resources with HPC (Intel PCM, MBM)
- Implemented an idle profiler that diagnoses off-cpu time in multi-threaded program using HPC
- Redesign chromium to block user tracking through web browser fingerprinting
- Contribute a project that aims to debloat chrome browser on the fly.

08/2019 - present

## Teaching assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech

• CS 6262: Network Security, Design and Implement the XSS task using node is and Chrome Extension

## **Open Source Projects**

04/2013 - present

### Committer at WebKit (patches)

- Implemented OpenGL ES backend for Accelerated Compositing.
- Developed memory pressure handler that copes with out-of-memory on top of Linux cgroup.
- Enhance WebGL support and Fix layout and rendering issues
- Fix CVE security bugs in WebKit

10/2013 - present

## **Member at GNOME foundation (patches)**

• Translate GNOME Web and its Help document in Korean

01/2015 - present

#### Contributor at Chromium/Blink (patches)

- Implemented a CSS spec called font-size-adjust
- Fix layout and rendering issues in blink

#### **Patents**

US 20110296323 Web page management method and apparatus and storage medium thereof
US 20110289110 Method of re-searching webpage and apparatus and storage medium therefor
US 20110093606 Interface method and display device
US 20110090165 Interface method and display device

#### **Presentations**

12/07/2014	Web Engines Hackfest 2014 in A Coruña, Spain (slides)
09/29/2014	DEVIEW 2014 in Seoul, South Korea (slides, video)
04/25/2014	Jeju University in Jeju, South Korea (slides)
10/27/2013	DevOn 2013 in Seoul, South Korea (slides)